<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.killbots</id>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">معركة الآليين</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Killbots </name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Robots asasinos</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">מתקפת רובוטים</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKillbotsxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Killbots</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Killbots</name>
  <summary>Outsmart the killer robots to win</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تغلب على الآليين للفوز</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Supera amb intel·ligència als robots assassins per a guanyar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Supera amb intel·ligència als robots assassins per a guanyar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Přechytračte ostatní roboty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Killermaschinen überlisten, um zu gewinnen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Γίνετε εξυπνότεροι από τα ρομπότ-δολοφόνους για να κερδίσετε</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Outsmart the killer robots to win</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Superruzu la murdistajn robotojn por venki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Sea más astuto que los robots asesinos para ganar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Võitmiseks on tarvis tapjarobotid üle kavaldada</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Garaitu errobot hiltzaileak irabazteko</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Voita päihittämällä tappajarobotit</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Soyez plus malin que les robots tueurs pour gagner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Se máis intelixente que os robots asasinos para gañar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">צריך להערים על הרובוטים הקטלניים כדי לנצח</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Siasati robot pembunuh untuk menang</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Supera in astuzia i robot killer per vincere</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">გასამარჯვებლად მკვლელ რობოტებზე ჭკვიანი მაინც უნდა აღმოჩნდეთ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">킬러 로봇을 뛰어넘어서 이기십시오</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Wees slimmer dan de killer-robots om te winnen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Lur deg unna drapsrobotane for å vinna</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przechytrz zabójcze roboty, aby wygrać</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Seja mais esperto que os robots assassinos para ganhar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Seja mais esperto que os robots assassinos para ganhar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Перехитрите роботов-убийц, чтобы выиграть</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Prekonajte zabijacích robotov, aby ste vyhrali</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Prelisičite ubijalske robote in zmagajte</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Överlista mördarrobotar för att vinna</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Kazanmak için katil robotları alt edin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Обдуріть роботів-вбивць, щоб виграти</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxOutsmart the killer robots to winxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">在智斗中胜过杀手机器人来获取胜利</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">利用您的機智贏過殺手機器人們</summary>
  <description>
    <p>How will you get away from the killer robots bent on destruction? Figure it out in this simple, entertaining game. You may be outnumbered by an endless stream of robots, but with your intelligence and handy teleportation device you can defeat them. Outsmart all of the killer robots to win and live to tell the tale!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">كيف تبتعد عن الآليين المصممين على التدمير؟ اكتشفها في هذه اللعبة المسلية البسيطة. قد يفوقنك في العدد ولكن بذكائك وجهاز النقل الآني سهل الاستخدام يمكنك هزيمتهم. تغلب على كل الآليين للفوز والعيش لتروي الحكاية!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Com aconseguireu escapar dels robots assassins propensos a la destrucció? Imagineu-ho amb aquest joc senzill i entretingut. Estareu superat en nombre per una munió sense fi de robots, però amb la teva intel·ligència i amb un dispositiu pràctic de teletransport els podreu guanyar. Supereu amb intel·ligència als robots assassins per a guanyar i viure per a explicar la proesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Com aconseguireu escapar dels robots assassins propensos a la destrucció? Imagineu-ho amb este joc senzill i entretingut. Estareu superat en nombre per una munió sense fi de robots, però amb la teua intel·ligència i amb un dispositiu pràctic de teletransport els podreu guanyar. Supereu amb intel·ligència als robots assassins per a guanyar i viure per a explicar la proesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Wie wollen Sie den Killerrobotern entkommen, die auf Zerstörung aus sind? Natürlich in diesem einfachen, unterhaltsamen Spiel. Sie sind vielleicht in der Unterzahl gegen eine endlose Anzahl von Robotern, aber mit Ihrer Intelligenz und Ihrem praktischen Teleportationsgerät können Sie sie besiegen. Überlisten Sie alle Killerroboter, um zu gewinnen und zu überleben. </p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Πώς θα ξεφύγεις από τα ρομπότ δολοφόνους που φέρνουν την καταστροφή; Ανακάλύψέ το με αυτό το απλό, διασκεδαστικό παιχνίδι. Μπορεί να σε κατακλύσει μια ατελείωτη ροή από ρομπότ, αλλά με τη νοημοσύνη σου και τη συσκευή τηλεμεταφοράς μπορεί να τα νικήσεις. Γίνετε εξυπνότεροι από τα ρομπότ δολοφόνους και επιβιώστε για να διηγηθείτε πώς τα καταφέρατε!</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">How will you get away from the killer robots bent on destruction? Figure it out in this simple, entertaining game. You may be outnumbered by an endless stream of robots, but with your intelligence and handy teleportation device you can defeat them. Outsmart all of the killer robots to win and live to tell the tale!</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Kiel vi foriros de la murdaj robotoj fiksitaj al detruo? Eltrovu ĝin en ĉi tiu simpla, amuza ludo. Vi eble estas plimultita de senfina fluo de robotoj, sed per via inteligenteco kaj oportuna teleportada aparato vi povas venki ilin. Superu ĉiujn murdrobotojn por venki kaj vivi por rakonti la rakonton!</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">¿Cómo escaparía de los robots asesinos y propensos a la destrucción? Resuélvalo en este juego sencillo y entretenido. Puede verse desbordado por una oleada interminable de robots, aunque puede vencerlos con su inteligencia y un práctico dispositivo de teletransporte. ¡Sea más astuto que los robots asesinos para ganar y sobrevivir para poder contarlo!</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Kuidas pääseda tapjarobotite eest, kes on saadetud just sind hävitama? Selles selle köitva mängu sisu peitubki. Lõputu robotite voog jätab sind alati vähemusse, kuid nutikuse ja mugava teleportatsiooniseadme abil on võimalik neist siiski jagu saada. Kavalda tapjarobotid üle ja jää ellu, kuni võid oma võidulugu kogu maailmale pajatada!</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Nola lortuko duzu ihes egitea robot hiltzaileen suntsipen ahalmenetik? Imaginatu ezazu hau jolas sinple eta dibertigarri honetan.  Robot kopuru amaigabe batek gainditu zaitzake, baina zure adimen eta telegarraioari esker hauek garaitu ditzakezu. Garaitu robot hiltzaile guztiak istorioa bizirik kontatzeko!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kuinka pääset pakoon tuhoasi tavoittelevia tappajarobotteja? Selvitä se tässä yksinkertaisessa mutta viihdyttävässä pelissä. Jäät ehkä robottien loputtoman tulvan alle, mutta älylläsi ja kätevällä teleportaatiolaitteella voit päihittää ne. Voita ja selviä kertomaan tarinasi olemalla tappajarobotteja nokkelampi!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Comment allez-vous parvenir à échapper aux robots tueurs qui cherchent à vous détruire ? Trouvez la solution dans ce jeu simple et amusant. Vous allez être débordé par une invasion infinie de robots, mais votre intelligence et votre téléporteur vous permettront de les vaincre. Soyez plus malin que les robots tueurs pour remporter la partie et raconter votre épopée aux générations futures !</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Como escaparás dos robots asasinos que traerán a destrución? Descúbreo neste xogo simple e entretido. Pode que un fluxo incesante de robots te supere en número, pero coa túa intelixencia e o teu dispositivo teleportador podes derrotalos. Se máis intelixente que os robots asasinos para gañar e vivir para contalo!</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">איך מתרחקים מהרובוטים הקטלניים שמנסים להשמיד אותך? זאת השאלה שצריך לפצח במשחק המהנה והפשוט הזה. אולי יש כמות גדולה של רובוטים סביבך אך החוכמה והתקן השיגור היעיל שלך יכולים להביס אותם. מערימים על כל הרובוטים וזוכים להעביר את המורשת הלאה!</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Bagaimana cara kamu bisa lolos dari robot pembunuh yang bertekad menghancurkan? Cari tahu di permainan sederhana yang menghibur ini. Kamu mungkin kalah jumlah dengan robot yang tak ada habisnya, tetapi dengan peranti teleportasi yang cerdas dan praktis kamu bisa mengalahkannya. Siasati semua robot pembunuh untuk menang dan hidup untuk menceritakan kisahnya!</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Come farai ad allontanarti dai robot killer votati alla distruzione? Scoprilo in questo gioco semplice e divertente. Potresti essere messo in inferiorità numerica da un flusso infinito di robot, ma potrai sconfiggerli con la tua intelligenza e con un pratico dispositivo di teletrasporto. Supera in astuzia tutti i robot killer per vincere e sopravvivere!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">როგორ გაექცეთ მკვლელ რობოტებს ნგრევის დროს? გაიგეთ ეს მარტივ, გასართობ თამაშში. თქვენ თავზე გადაგივლით რობოტების უსასრულო ნაკადი, მაგრამ თქვენი გამჭრიახობით და ტელეპორტაციის მოწყობილობით მათზე გამარჯვებაც შეგიძლიათ. იყავით უფრო ჭკვიანი, ვიდრე ისინი არიან და იცხოვრეთ, რომ ეს ისტორიები მოჰყვეთ!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">파괴의 신 킬러 로봇으로부터 어떻게 도망쳐야 할까요? 이 간단하고 재미있는 게임에서 알아 보십시오. 킬러 로봇이 끊임없이 공격해 오지만 전략적 움직임과 텔레포트로 로봇을 무찌를 수 있습니다. 킬러 로봇으로부터 살아남아서 전설을 이야기해 주세요!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Hoe weet u de killer-robots, gericht op vernietiging, te ontwijken? Zoek het uit in dit eenvoudige, onderhoudende spel. U kunt overweldigd worden door een eindeloze stroom robots, maar met uw intelligentie en handig apparaat voor teleporteren kunt u ze verslaan. Wees slimmer dan alle killer-robots om te winnen en leef om het te vertellen!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Korleis komma unna alle drapsrobotane som er ute etter deg? Det finn du ut i dette enkle men underhaldande spelet. Ein nær endelaus straum med robotar kjem mot deg, men med kløkt og ein hendig teleportør kan du slå dei. Kom deg unna alle drapsrobotane, så har du ei god historie å fortelja!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">W jaki sposób uciekniesz przed zabójczymi robotami nastawionymi na zniszczenie? Dowiedz się tego w tej prostej, wciągającej grze. Roboty mogą przeważać liczebnie, lecz dzięki twojej inteligencji i przydatnemu urządzeniu do teleportacji możesz je pokonać. Przechytrz wszystkie zabójcze roboty, aby wygrać i móc o tym snuć opowieści!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Como é que se poderá escapar dos robots assassinos focados na destruição? Descubra neste jogo simples e de entretenimento. Poderá ser sobrecarregado com uma sequência infinita de robots, mas com a sua inteligência e um dispositivo de tele-transporte útil, podê-los-á derrotar. Seja mais esperto que os robots assassinos para ganhar e sobreviver para contar a história!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Como você vai escapar dos robôs assassinos com focados na destruição? Descubra neste jogo simples e de entretenimento. Você poderá estar em desvantagem com uma sequência infinita de robôs, mas com a sua inteligência e um prático dispositivo de teletransporte, eles poderão ser derrotados. Seja mais esperto que os robôs assassinos para ganhar e sobreviver para contar a história!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Как спастись от роботов-убийц, которые всё уничтожают? Придумать выход поможет эта простая увлекательная игра. Роботы могут идти нескончаемым потоком, но их можно одолеть с помощью вашего интеллекта и полезного устройства для телепортации. Перехитрите всех роботов-убийц, чтобы выжить и поведать об этом!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Ako sa dostanete preč od robotov zabijakov určených na ničenie? Zistite to v tejto jednoduchej zábavnej hre. Možno vás prevyšuje nekonečný prúd robotov, ale pomocou svojej inteligencie a praktického teleportačného zariadenia ich môžete poraziť. Prekonajte všetky zabijácke roboty, aby ste zvíťazili, žili a rozprávali váš príbeh!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kako boste ubežali ubijalskim robotom, ki vas želijo uničiti. Ugotovite to v tej preprosti, zabavni igri. Verjetno se bo proti vam zapodila številčna premoč robotov, a s svojo inteligenco in priročno teleportacijsko napravo jih lahko premagate. Prelisičite vse ubijalske robote, da bi zmagali in živeli ter pripovedovali zgodbo!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Hur kommer du undan från mördarrobotarna inriktade på förintelse? Räkna ut det i det här enkla, underhållande spelet. Du kan vara övermannad av ett ändlös flöde av robotar, men med din intelligens och praktiska teleporteringsenhet kan du besegra dem. Överlista alla mördarrobotarna för att vinna och överleva så att du kan berätta om det.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Yok etmeye ant içmiş katil robotlardan nice kaçacaksınız? Bu eğlendirici, yalın oyunda bunu bulun. Sayısız robot üzerinize gelecektir; ancak zekanız ve kullanışlı ışınlanma aygıtınızla onları yenebilirsiniz. Öykünüzü anlatabilmek için robotları alt edin!</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Як втекти від роботів-вбивць, єдиною метою яких є руйнування? Спробуйте впоратися із цим завданням у нашій простій, але захопливій грі. Хай роботів дуже багато, але за допомогою вашого інтелекту та зручного пристрою для телепортування ви можете їх перемогти. Обдуріть вбивць, щоб виграти гру, і живіть далі, щоб розповісти світові вашу історію!</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxHow will you get away from the killer robots bent on destruction? Figure it out in this simple, entertaining game. You may be outnumbered by an endless stream of robots, but with your intelligence and handy teleportation device you can defeat them. Outsmart all of the killer robots to win and live to tell the tale!xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">如何从专事毁灭的杀手机器人手中逃脱？在这个简单有趣的游戏中找出来。这无尽的机器人流可能从数量上胜过你，但是依靠你的智慧和好用的传送设备你可以打败它们。以智慧胜过所有杀手机器人来获取胜利，活下来讲述你的故事！</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">您會如何逃離一心要摧毀您的殺手機器人呢？在這個簡單又好玩的遊戲裡探索吧。您可能會遇到無止盡的機器人，但是利用您的機智和一台傳送裝置您是可以贏過它們的。拼過所有殺手機器人的挑戰，然後活下來炫耀您的經驗吧！</p>
  </description>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+ and GFDL-1.3</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/killbots</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=killbots</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=killbots</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/killbots/killbots.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>killbots</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.killbots.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
